In the city light, flashing blues under New York nights
But his heart's up north where the river's run free
With a blonde hair, duty from April Country
He's got a badge of dream and a thing for a laugh
Caught a glimpse of her smile, now he's doing the math
From the Bronx to the Bush, oh he's thinking real deep
Pays are you the one I've been missing in my sleep
He said, she's gutting the trout, he's eating the steak
Somewhere in the middle they both take a break
He'd trade his knife stick for a fishing pole
Chase her laughter like it's his patrol, oh page
Don't you know you're the catch of the day
And this cop's got one hell of a line to say
on page where you fall in love with me
Yeah, oh my gosh, and we're back though the operation doesn't skip a beat you understand
30 inch cock 40 inch cock who is a fuck
Back
I mean it really didn't mean it's like because now it really doesn't even
matter because it's like I'm not monetized so it's like there's no like risk of anything it's like
Don't have to even worry about it. It's just just have to restart in five seconds and he's wasted all the time
That's a giant. That was a big one
A lot bigger. I think mine's probably
I have nightmares over that cock. It's been like how long six months of the same gigantic 30-inch black cock. It's huge
I swear it reminds bigger
Yours is bigger. Your big black cock is bigger. Yeah
Well, that makes sense
Because you did have like a bulge when you did the snow spangobana bullshit like you had a little family of squirrels in that
You have the biggest white talk on the planet
Who's this car
Yeah, I don't know be careful. She's be careful with that one. She's a wild one. That's be careful with all you
Throw me away
What is this, um, a new form of display? I see four of us. Oh, yeah
It's because it's because I don't see it on the TV though, mother of johnny baloney look
My little narco wife is
That's me, but I was a baby then I was younger
My me. Yeah, that was you when you were in your 20s. Yeah
I know, I know about that hair, that hair screams fucking Cali Cartel, screams, Cali Cartel baby, yeah.
So what's the story? Were we born, bombed?
Yeah.
Do the math, just look at the necklace alone, that necklace was worth more than dope planet and all things.
What you need, leave me alone.
Johnny what nothing would you have for breakfast you want to be alone your lunch
What are you doing?
She's hot
Oh, she left us alone.
One day, another day.
No, no, no, baby.
Again.
She says, you and me, look at that smile.
The fork eyebrows, that nose, that ridiculous chin.
Do you see what I'm to work you with, guys?
Stop, what are you doing?
You see the collar, the elbow, the collar bone, that's a suck on me, like a vampire.
She's got a nice firm chin, a jawline.
You know what I got right now?
I got a space between my front teeth too.
Do you?
Yep, a little sexy space.
That's cool, so they're falling out that means
Why didn't you say your earrings and like you buy a tooth to fill the gap I've had enough of your abuse
You know what?
We'll have a dental talk.
A dental talk.
We're talking about, you know, hygiene.
Dental hygiene.
A few.
Yeah.
Bologna.
I remember you.
I remember you from that panel.
I know.
And she was with that little Italian guy, the little Italian guy that he used to chase around.
It was a girl, but it looked like an Italian dude, the bitch from New Jersey, the little
member.
That's not you, is it?
I'm half like the girl that stayed in the bathroom for an hour one night on at least us live and she was like where'd she go
Remember them that girl. Yeah, we're gonna go down that road. Okay. What do you want to talk about?
Wait, that's you. No, that's not you. Okay. So what the hell?
I don't remember
No, she's not her dad owns a construction company. That's a spoilt little fucking bitch from New Jersey. She hasn't made
I don't know that girl has more money than Alicia. You're not will ever have
Dad
Bitch the little fat base they send out there like be her assistant
Yes
Yeah, what are you talking about those though her dad does if she doesn't have shit
Like everybody in New York right it's all about the pop-up. What did your dad do? I don't know I
Know are you one of those young my dad leave you a fortune when I was younger. He was the best
Hmm miss them. That's my name comes from when I was literally called me Joni baloney. That's why it's baloney
Yep
My pot baloney was my dog's name. Seriously
I swear to God, Mr. Bologna, Mr. B.
His name was Blaze when I adopted him,
but I changed it because of the little kid,
to Mr. Bologna, to like cute, yeah.
Little kids, it was 110 pound people,
pig nose, and they would walk up to him,
pull his nose, they would ride him.
What's your dog's name?
Mr. Bologna, Bologna, like Salami, yeah.
But when I met him, he was a killer.
I had to, yeah, I reformed them into a fucking lush
I gave him 14 years of my life he died March or 9th 2023 after 14
My bolognese. Oh, my baby
Oh, have you gotten another one since no why you're not ready. It's time. Yeah, I am ready
But I don't I did this or more I realized through him like you know, I will go to work it out from home
Well, I'm gonna like do like a lot of
I'm gonna see if I can I don't not like prayer work, but like I want him to send you one
or he could come back and he died in my own to my living room.
Oh my gosh, I hate this.
Yeah, my living room and I pulled him on to the yard. I tried to resuscitate him and he just peed all over himself and he died
I'm like, yeah, that's over. So I took a car a carpet
I rolled him in a carpet and took garbage bag roll them in the garbage bag and tied it up and left it in my backyard
It was March. It was cold. He froze overnight the next morning
I put my truck threw him in the back of the truck took him to Long Island and buried him under a tree
My boy Baloney, he was a good dog
Soon as he died Johnny in my arms. I just my brain went into he's garbage now. Isn't that cool?
Yeah
Because that's all you got to do. What are you gonna do sit there and cry? Oh my god
As soon as he died, I was like it's over. He's now garbage. I gotta get rid of this thing. Oh
Yeah, okay, but the way it's not baby
But now now 14 years. It was a good run. He's dead now
He's garbage if I don't get this thing out of my house in two hours. I'm gonna flies in here
It's garbage get rid of it. Okay, but wait no crying over that door and that's how you beat life, baby
You don't fucking cry over a little thing. Oh
Just realize what's going on and handle business move on
Stop.
You're still dead. Good, bury the shit.
It's garbage now.
What?
It's not coming back.
Mr. Bologna.
Mr. Baloney, are we gonna get another pit bull? Are we gonna get a different kind?
I'm gonna get like four of them, but just like a year or two. I still, you know,
you're gonna get one and you're gonna start
you're gonna get him where you get him like when he's like like not I rescued
him I rescued him they were gonna put him down Joanie. Yeah, yeah, well when he
was three years old they were gonna put him down when I met him he was in a
parking, go a killer. I teach young I said open the cage. They let him out he ran right by me
sniff my knee. I was like, All right, all right, my man already full size. Three years old. He was
fucking already to my fucking time. I took him for a walk around the block. I said I'll take him.
And I took him home with me. He never saw the inside of a cake ever again after that day.
Never, never. Ever. He stepped next to me on top of me for 14 years.
I saved him from that cage. I know you did and he saved you and now and he saved me exactly
We saved each other and now he's come and now he's coming back again, and I'm
Sometimes they can't come back inside
Yep, I was told that that my cat I have right now
This lady, I have a lady, if you believe me.
You went to us with a chip, me and Mr. Bologna.
I'm just telling you, I wasn't ready.
My cat had just passed away, I was freaking out,
and I happened to look, and I said,
what do you think about this one?
And she got a message, and she said
he wants to be called Joey this time.
And because it was the one that I took care of,
like three or four years ago.
And it's hard to say, okay, I don't know, I don't know,
but it was enough to make me pull the trigger and do it
so I wouldn't got him.
I'm still adjusting, it's been almost a year.
But what I'm saying is it came full circle
and I think this one is now too.
Yeah, this is
The ever coming up almost on three years now. This is ridiculous
Well, you would you just would do a walk-through one's gonna talk to you if you do a walk-through
Or you're gonna look it up you can even look on Craigslist and sometimes they get they got one or you could go to the rescue place
You don't have to pay a whole lot or nothing
One that just needs you they need you. Oh, I'm like pushing on you now. I've had it
That's what you need my neighbor so that don't for so long when I didn't have them they would tell me they're like you
I don't recognize you without the dog. No. Yeah, this was like it was next to me 24
I would take it to work that don't believe my fucking size. We're gonna get another so we're I'm gonna start looking for you
I'll have to talk to you private. I'm gonna start looking for I'm gonna ask for this. Yeah
Do you want a boy or girl?
So you just whatever talks to you, you're going to do a walkthrough.
Can you go back to that revenue?
You're going to, you're going to get, we're going to get...
Those are great families on earth.
The most loyal.
Johnny, they still jumped out of a car one day because people were yelling at me.
Okay?
Check this out.
I pulled up and I was talking to somebody like three people and the dog was in the car
and shotgun with the window open and they like were yelling at me.
We were having an argument.
The dog jumped out of the car came and started circling us growling about to kill them.
yeah my boy don't fuck around these dogs they're so loyal and loving it's incredible they're the most like
most powerful dog you can have and yet they're like the most gentle loyal creature at the same time
and the way they can discern I don't want you to get more than one right now please not with pit bulls
I just want you to get the one and and just
My bolognese that's when you put that name up alone. I know and that and I didn't plan on it
It was random. It was kind of like it grabbed it from my eye
It kind of like I typed it in like when I saw the picture and I was like, I don't know what I'm doing and
Yeah, it's kind of like meant to be
I literally had a conversation last night with somebody about it.
I'm like, you know, I miss my dog. I miss Mr. Baloney.
And they're like, you want another one? I'm like, I do.
But I don't think it's fair to him, like, whatever my schedule is.
No, no, it's totally fair. He wants you.
He wants, matter of fact, he may be the one coming back in spirit.
Or he wants, he wants to, he loves you that much.
This is stupid. I'm here to tell you.
He would do high-fives. He would do double high-fives. He could jump over my head
You're fucking rip your arms off. I have a job of a hat
2.0
You hear me?
Monster from heaven. Yeah from heaven. People will cross the street. They will see me coming with them
They will cross the street and I will look at them like you're such morons. Have you just met him?
You know like fear takes over
And then little kids little kids happen sighs would not be scared. Think about that how you might need so so like retorting humanity
humans men will cross the tree
No
You still live in the same place by that tree
Where the he was buried you are okay. Oh, no, no, no, but it's it's it's 15 minutes away 10 minutes away
No, I have
I have an accent to it, it's not like buried in a random place, it's at a house that you
Right, just like as a formality, we'll do a drive-by, like tomorrow or the next day
whenever, and maybe put like if you're not going to remove them from or you're going
to leave it, that's fine, but because it is like you say, well I was going to, I was
going to undig them in a couple of years and sell his bones.
Come on stop it what they said I could get three grand for bones people by bones Johnny. I'm gonna do
Don't know
And I'm gonna go to fucking Mohegan's son for the weekend. Atlantic City, baby.
Oh God, it's so hard to like go to the hotel room.
You imagine like going out with you, it'd be so hard to change.
You will not have time to talk after we eat and straight to kissing.
Straight to kissing into the hotel room.
Bubba, Bubba.
We're gonna kiss the whole way in the elevator or whatever it is.
I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna.
We'll be naked by the time we get in the room.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
And and you're gonna do a drive-by by the tree thing. I don't know if you want to dig them up right away
Let's just ceremonially work. Oh wait, you don't want me to fuck you
wait or manifesting
bringing the dog either the spirit of baloney or
It sounds like a cruise ship
Right here. I want to take it to the spirit of baloney. I've been saving all year
We're going to know the spirit of the baloney. Yeah, that's that's gonna be a honeymoon, baby
To the Bahamas
Spirit of balonies you want to take I told you she's crazy
Who comes up with that I did
Do something about it. Do something about it. Do something about it. Do something about it. Do something about it. Do something about it. Do something about it. Do something about it. Do something about it. Do something about it. Do something about it. Do something about it. Do something about it. Do something about it. Do something about it. Do something about it. Do something about it. Do something about it. Do something about it. Do something about it. Do something about it. Do something about it. Do something about it. Do something about it. Do something about it. Do something about it. Do something about it. Do something about it. Do something about it. Do something about it. Do something about it. Do something about it. Do something about it. Do something about it. Do something about it. Do something about it. Do something about it. Do something about it. Do something about it. Do something about it. Do something about it. Do something about it. Do something about it. Do something about it. Do something about
We had that much money. We could do that. We could actually get a
Well, you can buy a boat and just spray paint that on the back
Let's get the dog first. All right one step at a time
What dog you want to stick a kid on me? It's like having a child
Everyday the pork it poof. Come on. Nope. I'm not ready for that. I got my freedom back
Honestly when it died no as much as I was like, oh man. I was like, yes, I can breathe again
I swear to God
I was free the next day I buried him and I'm like holy shit. I don't gotta walk this dog 14 fucking years
Morning, I wake up at five in the morning before I go to work. I gotta walk him in the in the dark
I leave him. I gotta feed him. You know put his food all this shit. I gotta run home after work
I gotta worry about him all day. It's okay run home. Welcome. Take him to the park five times a day
Shit shit walk walk shit shit 14 years when he died
i'm not gonna lie there was a little part of me that was like finally this shit is over
so i'm not ready for another dog just yet baby you don't know what i went through with this
fucking dog and he wasn't on my first dog joanie i had many kids before him but this one okay this
one was like a marriage
Okay, so then there's good and bad with the marriage. Yeah, fuck that dog shit change the subject
I'm not getting a dog no time soon, baby. Unless fuck a cat. Hell no never
Getting peed in my house a little fucking
I'm here with the cat litter I got a coupon fuck the cat and the dog. This is Alex time
Fuck those felines and fucking mud
Why are you screaming?
It does because you don't get it through your only hands, baby, that's why.
So you get it.
Give me an Eric.
You're making my head vibrate.
See that picture?
Yeah, well, you look like you have a helmet on if I spray 52 in that shit in the Jeep you look like Lawrence Taylor from the Giants
That's it. I'm switching it, and I'm not gonna talk to you. You look like you would get on the Giants. Well, you said a helmet
What is that thing?
He you yeah
Literally you look like a woman
Dermot Thompson doing a full synth. If I spring my head blue and put a leaven on the side, that's full synth.
That's so mean, it's funny.
Oh my god, the neighbors are like sitting in it. They're calling the police.
Just tell them you're fucking all the time, all the fame of film fame.
Don't worry about it.
Oh, sir, you know, you're laughing and farting at the same time.
Look at you. Look at you.
We're waking up the whole building
Trying to put a dog on me like hold on I feel it well hold on did you feel the dog through the spirit of some shit?
Yes, okay. All right
Mr. Bologna
I'm gonna go get those bones. I need the dog. Yeah, he was a dog. He died and that's it baby. No
it's not that you know much time I gave to that fucking animal. Yeah, this is exactly how many
girls I went through with that dog. Yeah. Oh my god. He did give me a lot of pussy. I'll give
him that. Mr. Baloney got me a lot of pussy, baby. So my hands don't feel you. Nope. Nope. Mr. Baloney's
Mm-hmm. I'm gonna will it. I'm gonna make it happen
Don't I'm pretty magical if I really I I'm known ask somebody but that we both know I know how to hustle and get you
Yeah, yeah, I know how to find help. I know how to get you reservations
I'm the producer and I'm gonna work it out. Okay, so just get ready
Get ready
Bologna 2.0
So you like Darth Vader right? That hair comes off and there's just like a bolt head under there
We're fucking wires and shit, right? You Darth Vader bitch
Tomb Tomb Tomb Tomb Tomb Tomb Tomb that's how Johnny gets ready for a date
The chick comes out of a closet I'm fucking Tomb Tomb Tomb Tomb Tomb Tomb Tomb
This is just some sort of fetish shit, bro.
You only made it!
Not many people can get away with that shit and make me laugh.
So I'm taking it as a compliment, my friend.
I will, my little Dorsvigal baby.
I'll be normally crying, hanging out with you.
No, I don't care.
Don't you mean I won't love you?
I don't care that you're Dorsvigal.
Like fucking God, he just branded you Dorsvigal.
Thank you, God. Thank you, baby.
Join the dark side.
You're a dark journey, baby.
I've had it.
I'm coming back.
But you see it in your head, right?
The helmet coming down.
And she just gets jumbled.
They dropped the hair on her head, said the lipstick can't come...
Deep uses it, we have to go...
The night she comes home in disconcerts, they put the hair back in the...
Oh, God!
Okay, silence. Silence.
Oh, Joanie! See, just when I think I have been kidding her all night,
Gotti can come in with a missile, a tomahawk, and just boom!
Darth Joanie, you know? And just take the lead real quick.
So now, I'm gonna have to go back to the join board to beat Darth Joanie.
I
Just heard a cat
What are you laughing at your phone for
There you asshole. I've had it. I break it up with you. There's no more dogs. There's nothing but dark. Goodbye
See what you did
You do not know the power of the dark side Johnny now see what you did to me you took bologna away. How do you feel now?
I ain't gonna play with this. I'm not I'd be who's I be I am is who's I am
Cuz that's where I come from oh you went to get them on I'm yeah now I am huh I
Am I rise
I'm ghetto. Hey
Kept now
The cat from Bungus. Joey, what are you doing?
The cat was sound asleep until you got me all riled up.
Now he's like, please pull it on chords and everything else.
Leave my hair alone. I'm really, this is Campbell.
This is Johnny, this is Johnny picking you up.
John is here.
We're going on a cruise.
Ah, it's the dog, Joni!
Ready? Ready, fucker?
Come on, let's do it.
Mmm. Come on, Tommy, on the dock.
Oh, baby!
Owie, owie, owie, owie, owie.
Joni used to work on the dock!
It's love, it's love, it's love, it's love
She now works for downer all day, working for her man
She brings all her pain for love, no love
We're not forgetting Joni Storff Joni by the way
we got each other you psycho girl you you psycho motherfucker love you you
psycho bitch what did I do to end up with you oh god why do you hate me oh
God, thank you. Thank you for making me the albandi
What do you want back and still feel you peg
Remember when they were going to bed?
I can still feel you joining
So here we go in honoring of one of my past one of my past friends. You ready, baby
I'm buddy, baby. I was born ready. I was born ready
My little hot tamale
You have now want to speed down my baby
Oh, what's that? What's that dumb song? Midnight Love? Midnight Love? Midnight Love?
But at least I'm sure of all the things we got
Did the Christmas song?
What is it?
Right?
I don't know
It is?
Oh baby, here we go
We're off the radio, no rain beer and then listen
Alexa
Hey, we're off the radio
No rain beer, had a very bright shiny nose
And they'll make fun of them. They'll make fun of Roodle and then he'd like to slag you understand what Roodle means to me, baby
I was listening to that shit since fucking for three like oh, yeah, you want to laugh at the Chinese
Check out when I'm running the show you heard I'm gonna kill him in the show in the show
You go hit it Santa
at a very shiny nose.
Welcome to my head if you ever saw it.
You would even say it glows.
But all the other reindeer used to make fun of me.
They never let poor Rudolph join in any reindeer games
Until their one night when Rudolph said everyone's fucked
And you load up the glock, my peeps
I just blew every reindeer's head off, okay?
Listen to me, please.
It couldn't went that way.
It couldn't went the story, it couldn't went that way.
You're giving me a headache.
But it seems like Santa came and rescued Rudolph
before he blew everyone's head off in the fucking schoolyard.
I've had enough.
I'm gonna have to break up very soon.
I'm pulling out everything for you brother. I'm pulling out the kitchen sink and the bathroom sink
The closet clothes. I'm like that guy was saying a suit the pants don't fit
I throw it on the top of the lampshade. What do you want from my life?
Hold on to the rule of law everyone's head over the issue fear of slaying
What's up?
Hey, it's a song, baby.
Lady Gaga, run over by a reindeer.
Grandma.
Lady Gaga, radio.
No, not Lady Gaga.
You can't cut off a song in mid-summer.
Oh, that's a good one.
Play, Grandma, get run over by a reindeer.
I can't.
Can we hear Santa Claus is coming in town?
That's a good one.
That's an oldie, but a goodie.
Oops, she said it's too loud.
I
All right, I'm breaking up
Are we done?
No, I'm not baby cat is running around. He's now he's now knit a whole sweater
When I don't until you're fucking Joanie Darth Vader as that help me. Oh, I'm back to Joanie baloney
What do you want me you want me to be baloney or no no no you're Vader you're Vader
Whatever
What's his name go the guy that runs his joint hey joey all right, so are we going to bed yet or not?
Yo, baby, don't say that to me. Don't ever say that to me when we're not together. Are you trying to watch me do that?
Don't make me laugh. It's too late to laugh. I'm too early. All right, that's it. I'm not I'm not getting paid for this bit
Bring I can't bring all the content. Okay?
Hey, Nancy, go to bed. Nancy, go to bed. Nancy. Yeah, Nancy, go to bed. Nancy, go to bed.
Hey, Tony Bologna. Oh, whoa, whoa. Nancy Bologna. Now I'm wide awake. You got me all
jarred up. Damn. Fuck. We got, we got a couple of fleaks, black raccoon. They're all fuzzy.
They can't even get in here if they want it anyway. Yeah. The place is, is anybody even
Nobody's gonna save you
Johnny Baloney, why do you have to bring me to Baloney? Oh?
Hey, they smear
All right, I'm gonna be here. Oh, hey, they Samir. Yeah, what the hell's I mean? Is that a spell?
It's a Yiddish
Yiddish, okay
And you're done and now hold on and you're shining our Yiddish and you're done you're done
We're never done. I'm never gonna be done now when it's done on the panel you can go
I'll just be here by myself
Okay, yeah, you're gonna leave it on put it on 12 hours. He's sleeping. I know maybe oh, maybe oh wake up and play a song
When he goes to pee and like stumbles like the mess wakes him up
Yeah, why not, you know, why not? It's better than nothing. Oh, did you see that?
He stuck his head just for a second.